{
    "subject": "resource/Hasso_Plattner",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Berlin",
    "human_readable": "Hasso Plattner was born in Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8456454873085022,
            "question": "Where was Hasso Plattner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7708821296691895,
            "question": "Did Hasso Plattner attend university in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7108117341995239,
            "question": "In what century was Hasso Plattner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6703475117683411,
            "question": "Is Hasso Plattner German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41618335247039795,
            "question": "What is Hasso Plattner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2635978162288666,
            "question": "Where did Hasso Plattner's education take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23372392356395721,
            "question": "What kind of work did Hasso Plattner do early in his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2105865180492401,
            "question": "Is Hasso Plattner a successful entrepreneur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2087077647447586,
            "question": "What significant contributions did Hasso Plattner make to technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19692109525203705,
            "question": "What companies is Hasso Plattner associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hasso Plattner was born in Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7114_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant contributions did Hasso Plattner make to technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7114_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hasso Plattner a successful entrepreneur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7114_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did Hasso Plattner do early in his career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7114_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7114_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide multiple birth dates and locations for Hasso Plattner. However, a majority of them mention that he was born in either Berlin (1944) or January 21st (with one date conflicting with this information)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Hasso Plattner was born on January 21, 1944, in Berlin, Germany. Therefore, the statement that Hasso Plattner was born in Berlin is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}